for this back taper tutorial start two
fingers with your trimmer set your
guideline and remove the bulk continue
by polishing everything below that let's
shave about 90 of the area leaving a
little bit of room we're going to create
our first guideline with the lever open
this measures the half to erase it let's
soften it with our trimmer and let's
close our lever hit the beginning of the
guideline let's open it little by little
as we work our way up into the guideline
this is called close to open the second
guideline is going to be the one guard
with the lever open and let's soften it
first using the clothes to open with the
one guard so let's slightly open the
lever little by little then do the same
thing with the 0.5 guard so it's going
to be at the start of that second finger
so we could slightly open it little by
little to blend out that second line to
blend everything above that let's scoop
out using the number four guard lever
open three guard lever open the two
guard lever open and the last step is
going to be to blend everything out with
the 1.5 guard and slightly closing the
lever little by little to get this end
result right here